(this["webpackJsonpquiz-throne-of-glass"]=this["webpackJsonpquiz-throne-of-glass"]||[]).push([[0],{13:function(e,n,t){},14:function(e,n,t){},15:function(e,n,t){"use strict";t.r(n);var a=t(0),s=t.n(a),o=t(2),i=t.n(o),r=(t(13),t(3)),u=t(4),l=t(6),h=t(5),c=t(7),d=[{id:1,question:" What animal Rowan turns into?",options:["panther","hawk","wolf","dragonfly"],answer:"hawk"},{id:2,question:"What\u2019s the real name of Celaena Sardothien?",options:["Aelin Ashryver Whitethorn Galathynius","Aelin Ashriver Whitethorn Galathynius","Lysandra Ashryver n\xe9e Ennar","Aelin Ashryver Ennar Galathynius"],answer:"Aelin Ashryver Whitethorn Galathynius"},{id:3,question:"Where Aelin was born?",options:["Orynth","Rifthold","Eyllwe","Varese"],answer:"Orynth"},{id:4,question:"How old is Dorian in the first volume of Throne of Glass series?",options:["20","27","17","19"],answer:"19"},{id:5,question:"What\u2019s the name of Aelin\u2019s dog?",options:["Fire","Fleetfoot","Arrowhead","Tulip"],answer:"Fleetfoot"},{id:6,question:"What is Lysandra's occupation?",options:["assassin","carter","courtesan","baker"],answer:"courtesan"},{id:7,question:"Who is the first character mentioned by name in Heir of Fire?",options:["Chaol Westfall","Dorian Havilliard","Celaena Sardothien","Aelin Galathynius"],answer:"Celaena Sardothien"},{id:8,question:"What is the capital of Adarlan?",options:["Rifthold","Orynth","Varese","Meah"],answer:"Rifthold"},{id:9,question:"What clan does Asterin belong to?",options:["Yellowlegs","Fleetfoot","Purebloods","Blackbeaks"],answer:"Blackbeaks"},{id:10,question:"Where do the Thirteen stay and work in Queen of Shadows?",options:["Meah","Rifthold","Morath","Varese"],answer:"Morath"},{id:11,question:"What was the name of Rowan's wife?",options:["Lyria","Mab","Lysandra","Lyvia"],answer:"Lyria"},{id:12,question:"How many members does Cadre have in Heir of Fire?",options:["8","4","6","12"],answer:"6"},{id:13,question:"What eye color does Elide have?",options:["onyx","emerald","grey","amber"],answer:"onyx"},{id:14,question:"What is the name of Aedion's sword?",options:["Sword of Orynth","Morath","Goldryn","Damaris"],answer:"Sword of Orynth"},{id:15,question:"What is Dorian's fathers name?",options:["Hollin","Brannon","Dorian","Chaol"],answer:"Dorian"}];var m=function(e){return s.a.createElement(s.a.Fragment,null,s.a.createElement("h3",{className:"result_count"},"Game Over! Your final score is ",e.counter," points "),s.a.createElement("div",{className:"result_container-for-right-answers"},"The correct answer's for the questions was:",s.a.createElement("ul",{className:"result_list-right-answers"},d.map((function(e,n){return s.a.createElement("li",{className:"result_right-answers",key:n},e.answer)})))))};var w=function(e){var n=e.questions,t=e.options,a=e.handleCheckAnswer,o=e.myAnswer,i=e.currentQuestion,r=e.handleChangeQuestion,u=e.handleFinish,l=e.isFinished,h=e.counter;return l?s.a.createElement(m,{counter:h}):s.a.createElement(s.a.Fragment,null,s.a.createElement("h2",{className:"quiz-content_question-counter"},"Questions ".concat(i+1,"  out of ").concat(d.length," remaining ")),s.a.createElement("h1",{className:"quiz-content_question"},n," "),t.map((function(e){return s.a.createElement("div",{onClick:function(){return a(e)},className:o===e?"quiz-content_options selected":"quiz-content_options"},e)})),i<d.length-1?s.a.createElement("button",{className:"quiz-content_btn",onClick:r},"Next"):s.a.createElement("button",{className:"quiz-content_btn",onClick:u},"Finish"))},f=function(e){function n(){var e,t;Object(r.a)(this,n);for(var a=arguments.length,s=new Array(a),o=0;o<a;o++)s[o]=arguments[o];return(t=Object(l.a)(this,(e=Object(h.a)(n)).call.apply(e,[this].concat(s)))).state={currentQuestion:0,options:[],questions:"",answer:"",myAnswer:"",counter:0,isFinished:!1},t.loadQuizData=function(){t.setState({questions:d[t.state.currentQuestion].question,answer:d[t.state.currentQuestion].answer,options:d[t.state.currentQuestion].options})},t.handleChangeQuestion=function(){t.state.myAnswer===t.state.answer&&t.setState({counter:t.state.counter+1}),t.setState({currentQuestion:t.state.currentQuestion+1})},t.handleCheckAnswer=function(e){t.setState({myAnswer:e})},t.handleFinish=function(){t.setState({isFinished:!0})},t}return Object(c.a)(n,e),Object(u.a)(n,[{key:"componentDidMount",value:function(){this.loadQuizData()}},{key:"componentDidUpdate",value:function(e,n){var t=this;this.state.currentQuestion!==n.currentQuestion&&this.setState((function(){return{questions:d[t.state.currentQuestion].question,options:d[t.state.currentQuestion].options,answer:d[t.state.currentQuestion].answer}}))}},{key:"render",value:function(){return s.a.createElement("div",{className:"quiz-content"},s.a.createElement(w,{questions:this.state.questions,options:this.state.options,handleCheckAnswer:this.handleCheckAnswer,myAnswer:this.state.myAnswer,currentQuestion:this.state.currentQuestion,handleChangeQuestion:this.handleChangeQuestion,handleFinish:this.handleFinish,isFinished:this.state.isFinished,counter:this.state.counter}))}}]),n}(a.Component);t(14);var p=function(){return s.a.createElement("div",{className:"app"},s.a.createElement("h1",{className:"app_header"},"How well do you know Throne of glass series?"),s.a.createElement(f,null))};Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));i.a.render(s.a.createElement(p,null),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then((function(e){e.unregister()})).catch((function(e){console.error(e.message)}))},8:function(e,n,t){e.exports=t(15)}},[[8,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.c1012e5a.chunk.js.map